Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Records UA090
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Master's program field project reports, 1981 -- 2020; UA090.003; 145 Digital Object(s); 3 Linear Feet
  - Acquisition of Hazard Prone Coastal Properties as a Method for Coastal Resources Protection, 1993; UA090.003.001.00045; Carlisle, Bruce; Demit, Paul; Gregoire, John; Settles, Trish; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 45)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Department of Environmental Management
  - Transportation Voucher Program: A Proposal for Massachusetts, 1993; UA090.003.001.00046; Gouchoe, Susan; Reid, Sam; Rooks, Jennifer; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 46)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Executive Office of Environmental Affairs
  - Amazon Initiative: A Working Conference to Protect Indigenous Rights, 1993; UA090.003.001.00047; Chaudhury, Ina F.; Chester, Charles C.; Williamson, Laura E.; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 47)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Oxfam America
  - The Threat to Public Water Supplies from the Hazardous Materials Transportation Incidents, 1993; UA090.003.001.00048; Bodin, Ethan; Kowalski, Carol; Samimy, Roland; Weber, Sharon; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 48)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Water Resources Authority
  - Focus on the Future: Enhancing Youth Employment Opportunities, 1993; UA090.003.001.00049; Hirsch, Deva; Mori, Yasuko; Reidy, Alicin; Westheimer, Kim; Wright, Daryl; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 49)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Reaching Out to Chelsea Adolescents
  - Seeing the Face on Our Vegetables: A Feasibility Study for a Boston Multi-Farm community Supported Agriculture Program, 1993; UA090.003.002.00001; Fano, Alix; Mitchell, Alison; Reed, Clark; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 1)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Northeast Organic Farmers Association (NOFA), New England Small Farms Institute (NESFI)
  - Why Ukraine?: Opportunities and Challenges to Doing Business, 1993; UA090.003.002.00002; Caliandro, Birgit; Jenkins, Edith; Kennedy, Scott; Watt, Elaine McCormick; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 2)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: New England East West Trade Council
  - Perceptions of Global Resource Issues: Directions for Education and Outreach, 1993; UA090.003.002.00003; Blanchard, Elisa; Caner, Grace; Guillemin, Rob; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 3)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Union of Concerned Scientists
  - Swords Into Ploughshares: Sustainable Community Development in the Conversion of Fort Devens Army Base, 1993; UA090.003.002.00004; Cardona, Gloria; Goldstein-Gelb, Warren; James, Christine; Sagara, Carlton; Shapiro, Judith; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 4)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Boston Society of Architects
  - Fixing the Loops: Strategies for Recycling Market Development in Massachusetts, 1993; UA090.003.002.00005; Burt, Justine; Freidman, Eric; Goode, David; Saito, Osamu; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 5)
    1993 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Senator Stanley Rosenberg
  - Using Mediation in Massachusetts Environmental Disputes: An Effective Alternative for Resolution, 1993; UA090.003.002.00006; Cirillo, Nichole; Gascoigne, Jim; Matthews, Meighan; Rouleau, Denise; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Outreach for Health Behaviors: Pregnant Smokers and Smoking Cessation, 1994; UA090.003.002.00007; Nicolau, Maria; Jerome, Kitty; Kaplan, Kate Atkinson; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 7)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Cambridge, MA
  - Assessing Economic Development Needs of the Newcomer Business Community of Allston-Brighton, 1994; UA090.003.002.00008; Dalton, Kathy L.; Horton, Amy S.; Shields, Tom; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 8)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Allston-Brighton Community Development Corporation
  - Community-Based Employment and Training Models, 1994; UA090.003.002.00009; Chapman, Peter; Gardner, Alisa; Iida, Hanako; Michon, Steve; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 9)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Coalition for a Better Acre
  - An Assessment of the Massachusetts Toxics Use Reduction Act on the Coatings Industry, 1994; UA090.003.002.00010; Aquatella, Jean; Goldberg, Jay; Weltman, Eric; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 10)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: JSI Center for Environmental Health Studies
  - Vegetative Buffer Design for the City of Boston's Dorchester Composting Site, 1994; UA090.003.002.00011; Holdridge, Brian; Peterson, Michael; Serrano, Ellen; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 11)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Boston, Public Works Department
  - Fixing the Forest?: An Examination of U.S. Forest Service Management Practices in the White Mountain National Forest, 1994; UA090.003.002.00012; Arena, Kristine; Caffry, Susannah; Strell, Ethan; Wholley, Rebecca; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 12)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: U.S. Forest Service
  - A Report on Methods Used for Behavioral Motivation Assessment in the United States, 1994; UA090.003.002.00013; Carpenter, Julia; Wison, Jessica; Cano, Emilio; Sucre, Francisco; Henry, Snowden; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 13)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: USAID/World Wildlife Fund, Nature Conservancy & World Resources Institute
  - Gulf of Maine Whale Recovery and Implementation Plan for the Western North Atlantic: Humpback Whale (Megaptera novaeanliae) and Right Whale (Ebalaena glacialis), 1994; UA090.003.002.00014; Mooney-Seus, Marjorie; Nelson, Sean; O'Leary, Stephen; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 14)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Office of Protected Resources, National Marine Fisheries Service, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration
  - "Every Last Fish": The Large Marine Ecosystem and the New England Groundfish Industry, 1994; UA090.003.002.00015; Altman, Susan; Brown-Babcock, Maria; Le, Hue; Robinson, Cindy; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 15)
    1994 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Tufts Environmental Literacy Institute (TELI)
  - Plastic Lumber Purchasing Initiative: Investigation of Current Uses and Potential Uses in Massachusetts, 1995; UA090.003.002.00016; DiModica, John; Johnston, Dave; Yasuda, Yumiko; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 16)
    1995 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Department of Procurement and General Services
  - A Preliminary Assessment of the Bass River Harbor Area, 1995; UA090.003.002.00017; Gaffey, Denise; Heskett, Erin; Larsen, Andrea; Regmi, Pravignya; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 17)
    1995 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Beverly
  - Rural Economic Development in the Northern Forest: Defining Community Needs, 1995; UA090.003.002.00018; Chase, Mark; Hughes, Martin; Levin, Reva; Wilson, Wanda; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 18)
    1995 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Appalachian Mountain Club
  - Criteria for Successful Transit: Implementing an Alternative Fueled Municipal Shuttle in Cambridge, MA, 1995; UA090.003.002.00019; Basch, Rebecca; McElroy, Heather; Stein, Ellen; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 19)
    1995 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Cambridge, MA
  - Abandoned Building Survey Tool for Residential and Commercial Properties, 1995; UA090.003.002.00020; Albucher, Chelsea; Doub, Marian; Jimenez, Rowena; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 20)
    1995 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative (DSNI)
  - The Gardner Street Landfill Closure: Historical Significance and Current Public and Political Issues, 1995; UA090.003.002.00021; Al-Ghuiyy, Samira; Geer, Jackie; Siebens, Becky; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 21)
    1995 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Boston, MA
  - Child Care in Cambridge: Search for Long-Term Funding Options, 1995; UA090.003.002.00022; Basche, Fran; Hallinan, Dennis; Cronin, Kelley; Mack, Tony; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - A Tool for Assessing the Contribution of State, Local, and Institutional Policies to Agricultural Sustainability in Massachusetts' Connecticut River Valley, 1995; UA090.003.002.00023; Alterman, Michael; Murphy, James; Sherman, Robin; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 23)
    1995 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: The New England Small Farm Institute
  - Chapter 91 As a Harbor Planning Tool: Improving Waterfront Public Access in Provincetown, 1996; UA090.003.002.00024; Bishop, Kristen; Hargens, Andrew; Hoey, John; Rotondi, Michael; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 24)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Provincetown, MA
  - Joint Implementation: An Overview, 1996; UA090.003.002.00025; Emelianova, Lada; Kozak, Jennifer; Martin, Alejandra; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 25)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Recycling, Reciclaje, Reciclagem: Addressing Recycling Participation in the City of Somerville, 1996; UA090.003.002.00026; Chin, Helen; Jorge, Sonia; Melitsko, Graciela; Stern, Shari; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 26)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Somerville Environmental Protection Officer
  - Industry Efforts at Pollution Prevention in the Merrimack River Watershed: A Case Study for the Tufts Environmental Literacy Institute, 1996; UA090.003.002.00027; Boyd, Diane; Chandonnait, Peter; Murray, Brian; Raddatz, Alicia; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 27)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Tufts Environmental Literacy Institute (TELI)
  - 20/20: A "Greener" Vision for the Environment, The Role of the Retailer in Sustainable Production and Consumption, 1996; UA090.003.002.00028; Bennett, Judy-Ann; Boyer, M. Gabriela; Farrington, Melanie; Liu, Albert; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 28)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: World Business Council for Sustainable Development
  - A New Vision for Higher Education: Conceptual Strategies for Integrating Sustainability into Different Disciplines, 1996; UA090.003.002.00029; Beard, Heather; Callus, Megan; Pike, Lisa; Spier, Robbie; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 29)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client:
  - The Search for Land: Use Options On and Along Route 6 in Provincetown, 1996; UA090.003.002.00030; Giampe, Robert; Gruen, Darryl; Kissinger, Gabrielle; Schroeder, James; Weis, Mary; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Redeveloping Brown Fields: Case Studies in the Northeast, 1996; UA090.003.002.00031; Keohan, Jennifer; Luera, Michelle; McCoy, Keith; Meyer, Terry; Rose, Susan; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 31)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: The New York State Assembly Program and Counsel Staff
  - Micro Enterprise Initiatives: A Strategy for Economic Self-Determination, 1996; UA090.003.002.00032; Eldred, Darnae; Beeson, Elizabeth; Fiore, Maria; Parkes, S. Rhae; Wurster, Jill; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 32)
    1996 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Women's Institute for Housing and Economic Development
  - The Role of Science in Sustainable Communities: A Study of the Fishing Industry in Gloucester, MA, 1996; UA090.003.002.00033; D'Urso, Jen; Malcolm, Brian; Meyer, Sue; Newman, Julie; Sweeney, Ted; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Facing Water Scarcity: The Role of Industry in the Management of Fresh Water Resources, 1997; UA090.003.002.00034; Bauer, Dana; Myers, Jennifer; Moffett, Sam; O'Brien, Patrick; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 34)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: The World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD)
  - Open Space: The Final Frontier - A Study for the Open Space and Recreation Plan for the Town of Lynnfield, MA, 1997; UA090.003.002.00035; Archambeault, Laurie; Bowling, April; Bronars, Kris; Miller, Tracey; Press, Lisa; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 35)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Lynnfield, MA
  - Community Economic Development: Identified Needs, Lessons Learned and Suggested Strategies, 1997; UA090.003.002.00036; Haynes, David; Poley, Philip; Stokes, Jennifer; Woodburn, Brendan; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 36)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative (DSNI)
  - Tax Incentive and Loan Programs as Recycling Market Development Tools: Key Issues and Their Application to Massachusetts, 1997; UA090.003.002.00037; Jons, Pamela; Justus, Stacey; Keller, Debora; Mirza, Kathi; Petlin, Gabriel; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 37)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: MassRecycle, Inc., The Massahusetts Recycling Coalition
  - To Plant a Seed: Cultivating Community and Growing Connections, 1997; UA090.003.002.00038; Goldin, Gayle; Patrick, Jennifer; Whelan, Kristen; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 38)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: The Somerville Community Growing Center, Somerville Community Gardens
  - The Sustainable Building Demonstration Project: Compilation of a Product Manual, 1997; UA090.003.002.00039; Cooper, Carolyn; Grossman, Glenn; Roth, Katherine; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 39)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client:
  - Medford Early Childhood Care and Education Assessment Project: A Report on the Medford Community Needs Assessment for Early Childhood Care and Education Services, 1997; UA090.003.002.00040; Atwood, Annie Baker; Carvelli, Donna; Elson, Dean; Holmes, Jacquelyn; Olivo, Carisa; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 40)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Medford Family Resource Coalition
  - Fish in the City: Challenges Facing the Mystic River Herring Run, 1997; UA090.003.002.00041; Burtner, Jason; Clish, Heather; Kimball, Nicole; Nordgren, John; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 41)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Alewife/Mystic River Advocates
  - Volunteer Monitoring Manual, 1997; UA090.003.002.00042; Brukilacchio, Lisa; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Creating Sustainable Buildings, 1997; UA090.003.002.00043; Vitulli, Angela; Landman, Miriam; Hayano, Akiko; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 43)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Operational Services Division (OSD), Massachusetts Division of Capital Planning and Operations (DCPO)
  - Literature Review for Management Consulting Services, 1997; UA090.003.002.00044; Barry, David; Lin-Marcus, Peter; O'Connor, Kathleen; Outar, O'Neil; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Policy and Program Guide for GrandFamilies, 1997; UA090.003.002.00045; Besser, Marla; Nettleton, Kathryn; Stavsky, Sasha; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 45)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Boston Aging Concerns -- Young & Old United, Inc. (BAC-YOU, Inc.)
  - A Preliminary Exploration of Issues for the Development of an Urban Aquaculture Institute for Boston Harbor, 1997; UA090.003.002.00046; Bonta, Marc; Duvvuri, Vijaya; Garland, Charlene; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 46)
    1997 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: New England Aquarium
  - The Vieques Field Project Report, 1998; UA090.003.003.00001; Barahona, Xenia; Mateo, Elena; Meyer, Johanna; Pelton, Darryl; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 1)
    1998 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Economist Allied for Arms Reduction
  - Natural Systems and Land Use Inventory and Analysis: Newbury, MA, 1998; UA090.003.003.00002; Ford, Todd; Jameson, Darcy; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 2)
    1998 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Newbury Planning Board
  - Open Space and Recreation Plan, 1998; UA090.003.003.00003; Archambault, Laurie; Bowling, April; Bronars, Kris; Miller, Tracey; Press, Lisa; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 3)
    1998 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Lynnfield, MA
  - Preserving Cape Cod's Past for the Future: A Cultural Landscape Study of Bourne, Sandwich, and Falmouth, 1999; UA090.003.003.00004; Hevenor, Martha; Prokop, Ambika; Robillard, Nicole; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 4)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Cape Cod Commission
  - Synergies of Rio Agreements (UNFCCC, CBD & UNCCD) and its Implementation in India, Namibia, Netherlands, and Philippines, 1999; UA090.003.003.00005; Augusto, Angela; Chan, Winnie; Davis, Michaele; Greaves, Natasha; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 5)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Biodiversity action Network (BAN)
  - Schmalz House: A Proposal for a Demonstration Project for the Tufts Climate Initiative, 1999; UA090.003.003.00006; Blair, Robert; Kollmuss, Anja; Perry, Anne; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 6)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Tufts Facilities, Tufts Institute for the Environment (TIE)
  - The Clean Environment Fund: Supporting Recycling Efforts in Massachusetts, 1999; UA090.003.003.00007; Cohen, Dan; Hassan, Alyssa; Nikolayev, Dmitriy; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 7)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: MassRecycle, Inc.
  - Arts, Culture, and Economic Development: Experiences in Boston and Beyond (Madison Park Field Project), 1999; UA090.003.003.00008; Beyene, Tina; Dobrowolski, Tania; Murphy, Tara; Rivera, Federico; Zucconi, Tanya; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 8)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Arts, Culture, and Trade Roxbury Consortium